hi I'm Marcus gremlin I'm one of the
嗨，我是Marcus gremlin，我是其中之一
architects and developers of the JDK
JDK的架构师和开发人员
flight recorder a feature included in
飞行记录器中包含的功能
JDK 11 I'm going to give you a quick
JDK 11我要给你个快速
overview of what this feature is what it
此功能是什么的概述
is decide to do and give you some hands
决定去做，给你一些帮助
on in order to demonstrate how it can
以演示如何
assist us solving problems
协助我们解决问题
what is the JDK flight recorder the most
什么是JDK飞行记录仪？
intuitive way to understand it is to use
理解它的直观方法是使用
the analogy of the recording device in
记录设备的类比
an aircraft and just like these devices
一架飞机，就像这些设备
record interesting events related to air
记录与空气有关的有趣事件
travel flight records intended to record
打算记录的旅行航班记录
events related to our programs what is
与我们的计划有关的事件是什么
being recorded our events and we can
记录我们的事件，我们可以
think of an event as some piece of data
将事件视为某些数据
at a particular instant of time
在特定的时间
recording events using flight recorder
使用飞行记录器记录事件
allows us to persist a representation of
使我们能够坚持
the execution States in time periods
时间段内的执行国
just before and during a problem this
就在问题之前和期间
entails we can later go back in time if
需要我们稍后再回溯
you will to understand what was leading
您将了解导致什么的
up and happened just prior to some
发生在一些之前
problem or less than optimal situation
问题或低于最佳情况
the key to flight record has been able
飞行记录的关键已经能够
to record high quantities of information
记录大量信息
while keeping the overhead of the
同时保持
recording process low the system is
录音过程低系统
designed to run always-on in
设计为始终在线运行
mission-critical environments another
关键任务环境另一个
very important design goal has been to
非常重要的设计目标是
help speed up the time it takes to start
帮助加快启动时间
the process of problem analysis thereby
问题分析过程
cutting the overall time for issue
缩短发布时间
resolution flight recorder tries to
分辨率飞行记录仪试图
accomplish this by recording information
通过记录信息来完成此任务
that would highlight our system from
这将从以下方面突出我们的系统
many different perspectives ranging from
许多不同的观点
informational overviews such as command
信息概述，例如命令
line parameters loaded modules and
线路参数加载模块和
system properties to some very detailed
系统属性要非常详细一些
information regarding say the time
关于时间的信息
waiting to acquire a monitor or the time
等待获取监视器或时间
spent executing a piece of code during
在执行期间花了一段代码
subsequent analysis we can therefore
因此，我们可以进行后续分析
start out from a holistic perspective
从整体角度出发
and drill ever deeper into the relevant
并深入研究相关
details JFR is especially up for
详细信息JFR特别适合
recording latencies where traditional
记录传统的延迟
profilers report time executing j4
分析器报告执行j4的时间
records a report situation where the
记录报告情况，其中
application is not executing or at least
应用程序未执行或至少
not as effective as it could be another
不如另一个有效
design goal
设计目标
to provide insight into how programs
深入了解程序
interact with the execution environment
与执行环境互动
as a whole as you are most certainly
总体上来说，您肯定是
already aware many problems we run into
已经意识到我们遇到的许多问题
are not directly attributable to logical
不直接归因于逻辑
errors in our programs but they appear
我们程序中的错误，但它们出现了
because of our confluence and
因为我们的融合
manufactures in relations with flight
与飞行有关的产品
recorder we have a means to capture
记录器，我们有一种捕获方法
these usually hard to reproduce
这些通常很难复制
situations where a large portion only
只有很大一部分的情况
seems to surface in production
似乎在生产中浮出水面
environments
环境
the most common use case is to use JFR
最常见的用例是使用JFR
as a background recorder analogous to
作为类似于
the recording device in aircraft we can
飞机上的录音设备
also view the flight recorder
同时查看飞行记录仪
infrastructure as providing us with an
基础设施为我们提供了
always available profiler ready to
随时可用的探查器
record more extensive information if
记录更多信息，如果
needed and maybe only for a short period
需要，也许只是短期的
of time the actual interaction with
与时间的实际互动
flight recorder is very simplistic the
飞行记录仪非常简单
work we invest is done prior to and
我们投资的工作在完成之前和
after getting the recording system
获得录音系统后
running in the former case we designer
在我们设计的前一种情况下运行
events and metadata using the api's and
使用api的事件和元数据
in the latter we make use of the
在后者中，我们利用
recorded information in order to improve
记录信息以改善
our understanding of a system at a
我们对系统的理解
particular time or in a particular
特定时间或特定时间
situation and this can be especially
情况，这可能尤其
helpful in production environments to
在生产环境中有助于
get data out from flight recorder we
从飞行记录仪中获取数据
instruct it to dump the information that
指示它转储该信息
has already recorded and this produces a
已经录制了，这会产生一个
binary file which we can view as a
二进制文件，我们可以将其视为
database in compressed format we can use
我们可以使用压缩格式的数据库
programmatic api's for interacting with
与之交互的程序化api
this file and this can be useful if you
此文件，如果您
already have some sense of what we're
已经对我们有一些了解
looking for but mostly you don't like
寻找，但大多数时候你不喜欢
any good profile you put to use it will
您投入使用的任何好的配置文件都会
almost invariably point you somewhere
几乎总是将您指向某个地方
when you have no idea of even start
当你连开始都不知道的时候
looking in these situations we can
在这些情况下，我们可以
enlist the help of a GUI to assist us
寻求GUI的帮助来协助我们
manage and better understand the large
管理并更好地了解大
data sets and relations so let's use
数据集和关系，让我们使用
Jakob and we will use Jacob and Pitt
雅各布，我们将使用雅各布和皮特
help and we can see five commands for
帮助，我们可以看到五个命令
interacting with JFR the command to
与JFR交互的命令
start recording is called j4 start
开始录音称为j4开始
here I've given this first recording a
在这里，我给了这首录音
name called continuous because this will
之所以叫连续，是因为
be the recording we will have running in
是我们将要运行的录音
the background by having this recording
通过录制此背景
running we can send requests to dump the
运行中，我们可以发送请求以转储
recorded information anytime we like and
随时记录信息，并且
that is exactly what we'll do here after
这正是我们在这里要做的
letting it record for a while
让它记录一段时间
we use the j4 dump command to get the
我们使用j4 dump命令获取
information from flight recorder so
来自飞行记录仪的信息
let's use that here j4 dump name
让我们在这里使用它j4转储名称
continues file name and let's call this
继续文件名，我们称之为
one discovery doc j4 that's again issued
再次发布的一个发现文档j4
the j4 check command notice here that
j4检查命令注意这里
the dump operation we just completed is
我们刚刚完成的转储操作是
non-destructive in the sense that we
在我们无损的意义上
still have a background recording
仍有背景录音
running now just a quick note in the
现在运行，只是在
file we just dumped a recording file
文件我们刚刚转储了一个录音文件
contains much structure in this example
在这个例子中包含很多结构
here we have a sample file of about five
这里我们有大约五个样本文件
Meg's in size I've used the API sin JDK
梅格大小我用过API sin JDK
J for consumer to reconstruct the
J供消费者重建
relational information into two standard
关系信息分为两个标准
file formats JSON and XML the file size
文件格式JSON和XML文件大小
listings give testimony to the fact that
清单证明了以下事实：
although the the file can be transformed
虽然文件可以转换
into these are the format's you need to
这些是您需要的格式
be aware of the size overheads now we
现在要注意大小开销
will start our analysis and in order to
将开始我们的分析，并为了
properly understand the vast amount of
正确理解大量
information we have at our disposal we
我们掌握的信息
prefer to use a GUI tool that will
宁愿使用GUI工具
assist us with the analysis process we
协助我们进行分析
will use JDK Mission Control which is an
将使用JDK Mission Control
excellent tool for doing just this and
做到这一点的优秀工具
just us with flight recorder with four
只是我们有四个飞行记录仪
JDK 11 JDK Mission Control has been open
JDK 11 JDK Mission Control已打开
source and donated by Oracle to the open
源并由Oracle公开捐赠
JDK community we will be using an early
JDK社区，我们将尽早使用
access version of Mission Control
访问版本的任务控制
let's click the threads tab here to the
让我们单击此处的“线程”选项卡
left we can see threads being
离开我们可以看到线程正在
represented as rows in a table each row
表示为表格中的每一行
is projected onto the graph
投影到图上
representative execution state for that
代表执行状态
particular thread in the graph itself we
图本身中的特定线程
can see time plotted along the x-axis
可以看到沿x轴绘制的时间
these graphs remind me of sonar graphs
这些图让我想起了声纳图
you know the kind they use in underwater
你知道他们在水下使用的那种
seabed explorations and just like Sona
海底探险，就像索纳（Sona）
grafts help to pick the contours of
嫁接有助于挑选轮廓
something we cannot directly observe so
我们无法直接观察到的东西
jf4 can help us see contours of hard to
jf4可以帮助我们看到很难
observe problematic execution patterns
观察有问题的执行模式
we also see quite a number of red dots
我们还看到了很多红点
these red dots are events let's inspect
这些红点是让我们检查的事件
what kind of event it is Java monitor
Java监视器是什么样的事件
blocked besides giving us information
除了向我们提供信息外
about how long this thread was blocked
关于该线程被阻塞多长时间
before acquiring on the monitor it also
在监视器上获取之前
gives us information about the monitor
向我们提供有关显示器的信息
itself for example it gives us the
本身例如它给我们
instance of the monitor that is it's
监视器的实例是
represented by the monitor address it
由监视器地址代表它
also gives us the class for this
也给我们上了这个课
instance and here it is a Java util hash
实例，这是一个Java util哈希
table in addition it gives us
桌子还给我们
information about what thread was the
有关什么线程是的信息
previous owner of the monitor when
监视器的先前所有者
monitor blocked events line up like this
监视被阻止的事件像这样排队
vertically it's a clear indication of a
在垂直方向上，这是一个明显的指示
bottleneck it looks like most threads
瓶颈看起来像大多数线程
needs to acquire this particular monitor
需要购买此特定的监视器
in order to proceed with execution down
为了继续执行下去
the right that is along the time axis
沿时间轴的右边
let's select one of these events here
让我们在这里选择这些事件之一
the stack trace view provides us with
堆栈跟踪视图为我们提供了
great contextual information we
我们提供的重要上下文信息
instantly see that this thread is
立刻看到这个线程是
blocked while execute in this particular
在执行此特定操作时被阻止
path mission controls are provides
提供路径任务控制
another view over locks so let's check
锁的另一个视图，让我们检查一下
that one as well
那一个
and now let's check the code related to
现在让我们检查与
this
这个
why indeed it looks like we're using a
为什么确实看起来像我们在使用
plain old hash table to store our log
普通的旧哈希表来存储我们的日志
entries with hash table being
哈希表为
synchronized we immediately see our
同步，我们立即看到我们的
mistake let's change it to a concurrent
错误，我们将其更改为并发
hash map instead we're just about to
哈希地图，相反，我们只是要
deploy our new code what we remembered
记住我们的新代码
that we might want to turn on j4 from
我们可能想从打开j4
the start we do another dump for this
首先，我们为此做另一个转储
newly deployed code which I'm not
新部署的代码，我不是
showing here and we again check the
显示在这里，我们再次检查
threads tab look ma no dots in this
线程选项卡看起来没有任何点
example of course I knew where to start
我当然知道从哪里开始的例子
looking but sometimes you don't the good
看起来，但有时你不好
thing is that Mission Control can
问题是任务控制可以
actually assist us with this kind of
实际上可以帮助我们
analysis we will redo the same scenario
分析，我们将重做相同的场景
that we just did but at this time we
我们刚刚做过，但此时我们
will check the automated analysis
将检查自动分析
results page one rule here says look
结果页的一条规则在这里说
instances Java blocking and it looks
实例Java阻塞，看起来
like it automatically found the hoenn
像它一样自动找到了nn
number of threads being blocked on this
被阻塞的线程数
particular monitor let's pause here why
特定的显示器让我们在这里暂停
do we not see this until production
在生产之前我们看不到吗
either we didn't provoke enough stress
要么我们没有引起足够的压力
during testing to increase the
在测试中增加
concurrency level to a problematic level
并发级别到有问题的级别
or maybe we did do that but we did not
或者也许我们做到了，但是我们没有
use a tool that reported about it during
使用在此期间报告此问题的工具
the test cycle in this situation the
在这种情况下的测试周期
code we were involved with was a was a
我们参与的代码是一个
wrong so we could easily change it but
错误的，所以我们可以轻松地更改它，但是
it could just as well as big code
它可能和大代码一样好
located in our library that we were
位于我们的图书馆
using we believe JFR can be of
使用我们认为JFR可以
assistance here helping us scale this
这里的帮助可以帮助我们扩展规模
value say we wanted to report this
值说我们想报告这个
finding to the library developers we
向图书馆开发商寻找我们
could easily attach this recording to
可以轻松地将此录音附加到
their bug reporting system now the bug
他们的错误报告系统现在是错误
report just got stronger our argument
报告只是加强了我们的论点
being backed by empirical evidence the
得到经验证据的支持
library developers in their turn is also
图书馆开发者也
in a much better position they have just
他们处于更好的位置
received a piece of real execution about
收到了关于
how their library is being used and
如何使用他们的图书馆，以及
again from a production environment
再次从生产环境
another philosophical reflection is that
另一个哲学思考是
there was no real error involved here we
这里没有真正的错误，我们
ended up in a problematic situation
最终陷入困境
because we missed a few
因为我们错过了一些
let's see if we can get some additional
让我们看看是否可以得到一些额外的东西
information from this file let's click
单击此文件中的信息
the memory tab while we see here is a
内存选项卡，而我们在这里看到的是
sawtooth graph representing heap memory
表示堆内存的锯齿图
usage in this VM each cycle consists of
此VM在每个周期中的使用情况包括
a build up face which represents a
代表一个
period of heap memory allocations
堆内存分配期
followed by a subsequence sharp drop
随后是子序列的急剧下降
which represent a GC and then the cycle
代表GC，然后是循环
starts over the frequency of this graph
从该图的频率开始
seems to be around 2 Hertz that is we
似乎在2赫兹左右
have two cycles per second if we expect
如果我们期望每秒有两个周期
this in more detail we can see at the
这一点我们可以在
start of a cycle our heap usage is
一个周期的开始，我们的堆使用情况是
around 570 Meg's at the end of the cycle
周期结束时约有570兆欧
our heap usage has now grown to
现在我们的堆使用量已增长到
approximately 2.4 gigabytes
约2.4 GB
this gives us an allocation rate of
这给我们分配率是
about 4 gigs per second another valid
大约每秒4演出另一个有效
inference we can make is that most of
我们可以推断的是，大多数
these allocations are short-lived
这些分配是短暂的
objects the reason for this claim is
反对此主张的原因是
that the GC is able to push down the
GC能够降低
heap back to the starting position at
堆回到起始位置
each cycle we can get another piece of
每个周期我们可以得到另一个
important information if we click the
重要信息，如果我们单击
garbage collection check box now for
现在的垃圾收集复选框
something with the information about GC
关于GC的信息
pause times what we see is that GC has a
暂停时间，我们看到的是GC具有
post time of about 20 milliseconds what
发布时间约20毫秒
this means for us in this context is
对我们而言，这意味着
that the GC stopped our application for
GC停止了我们的申请
about 20 milliseconds to do its work but
大约需要20毫秒才能完成工作，但是
since we have two of these G C's per
因为我们每个G C有两个
second we actually have a post time of
第二，我们实际上有一个发布时间
40 milliseconds per second in this
每秒40毫秒
application at this point we would like
此时我们想要的应用程序
to understand what objects are being
了解什么物体
allocated and from where Jeff our
分配和杰夫我们从哪里
provides us with the ability to the
为我们提供了
object allocation sampling without
不进行对象分配抽样
bytecode instrumentation but in order to
字节码检测，但是为了
get this information we will need to
获取此信息，我们将需要
enlist the profiling capabilities of the
征集
j4 engine since the sampling mechanism
j4引擎自采样机制
has a slight overhead and can generate a
开销很小，会产生
lot of data it does not turn on by
无法打开的大量数据
default instead it is included in our
默认而是包含在我们的
settings for our doing a profile
我们进行个人资料的设置
recording
记录
we will start an additional recording
我们将开始其他录制
and we will explicitly pass the settings
我们将明确通过设置
to do a profile recording to JFR with
用...将档案记录到JFR
this heavy rate of allocation though we
如此高的分配率，尽管我们
only need to have a very short sample to
只需要一个非常短的样本即可
understand what might be allocating so
了解可能会分配什么
we will also unless another option there
我们也将除非有其他选择
is called duration which lets us each
被称为持续时间，让我们每个人
schedule a time-based recording and
安排基于时间的录制并
let's just run it for one minute at the
让我们在它上运行一分钟
end of this minute JFR will stop and
此分钟结束时，JFR将停止，
dump the recording to the file name we
将录音转储到我们的文件名
specify and here we name it
指定并在这里命名
allocation the GFR we open allocation j4
分配GFR，我们打开分配j4
in JMC and we can see that our top
在JMC中，我们可以看到
section has been populated by
部分已由填充
information about allocations here all
所有有关分配的信息
the sample instances are grouped
样本实例已分组
according to class and we can see that
根据班级，我们可以看到
the top candidate seems to be a boolean
最佳候选人似乎是布尔值
array trick mark this boolean array we
数组技巧将这个布尔数组标记为
can see in the stack trace below the
可以在下面的堆栈跟踪中看到
actual allocation sites aggregating onto
实际分配地点汇总到
these allocations and here it seems that
这些分配，这里似乎
there is only one single allocation site
只有一个分配站点
let's inspect this code this section of
让我们在本节中检查此代码
the application is involved in
该应用程序涉及
calculating prime numbers and we saw
计算素数，我们看到
that j4 pinpointed the allocation site
j4查明了分配站点
from the boolean and race to the line
从布尔值到种族
number 35 of the Eratosthenes algorithm
Eratosthenes算法的数字35
and here the boolean array has been used
这里使用了布尔数组
as the sifting array having had this
作为具有此的筛选数组
site pinpointed to us but j4 has been
该网站指向我们，但j4已经
related to high frequency of GCS and
与GCS的高频率有关
consequently of GZ pulse times we can
因此，以GZ脉冲时间我们可以
now start to think how it could make
现在开始思考它如何使
this application more effective maybe by
此应用程序可能更有效
redesigning this piece of code to not
重新设计这段代码
allocate us frequently maybe by using a
经常通过使用
caching technique or some kind of
缓存技术或某种
memorization we would be able to much
记住，我们将能够
more effective where we're involved in
我们参与其中更有效
the analysis of this level it's very
这个级别的分析非常
easy to lose track of the bigger picture
容易迷失大局
we might think well what's 40
我们可能会想好40
milliseconds should try to always remind
毫秒应尽量提醒
ourselves of the concept of scale so
我们自己的规模概念
let's try to answer this question
让我们尝试回答这个问题
what's 40 milliseconds 40 milliseconds
什么是40毫秒40毫秒
is 4% 4% of the time our application is
是4％4％的时间是我们的应用程序
not doing anything
什么也没做
it is pause because of GC activity 4% of
由于GC活动的4％，因此暂停
24 hours is almost one hour 4% of a week
24小时几乎是每周一小时的4％
is almost 7 hours so 7 hours per week
将近7个小时，所以每周7个小时
this application is not doing any useful
该应用程序没有任何用处
work let's say we've deployed hundred of
假设我们已经部署了数百个
these instances so 700 hours per week
这些实例，所以每周700小时
our application sibling is sitting idle
我们的应用程序同级闲置
now if you also had some business model
现在，如果您还有某种商业模式
we could extend this thought experiment
我们可以扩展这个思想实验
by by factoring in a monetary value per
通过考虑每个货币的价值
compute hour so if we can just figure
计算小时数，以便我们能算出
out a way to maybe have just a single GC
可能只有一个GC的方法
happen every second or that we can get
每秒发生一次，或者我们可以得到
there pause times down to 10
停顿时间降至10
milliseconds we would have improved our
毫秒，我们会改善我们的
effectiveness by 350 hours per week
每周350小时有效
closing out this brief demonstration
结束这个简短的示范
there's one more piece that I would like
还有一件我想要的
to show you I searched a decade knowing
告诉你我搜索了十年
we provide Java API that allows you to
我们提供Java API，可让您
create your own application specific
创建自己的特定于应用程序
events into JFR although I will not have
事件进入JFR，尽管我没有
the time here to demonstrate how to
在这里演示如何
program using the API I would like to
我想使用API​​的程序
show you an example what a custom event
向您展示一个自定义事件的示例
might look like as you remember my
可能就像您记得我的
application has a section that involves
应用程序的一部分涉及
calculating prime numbers and here we
计算素数，在这里我们
can see a custom event I added two JFR
可以看到我添加了两个JFR的自定义事件
to represent these calculations there's
代表这些计算，有
a lot of details here that might need to
这里有很多细节可能需要
cover some other time but the main
涵盖其他时间，但主要
takeaway message is that there is no
外卖消息是没有
categorical difference between this
这之间的绝对区别
custom event and the events we've been
自定义事件和我们去过的事件
inspecting so far of course it might
到目前为止检查当然可以
look that way but that is because JMC
看起来像那样，但这是因为JMC
has predefined views of some of the most
有一些最预定义的视图
general event types this view also
一般事件类型此视图也
demonstrates another important aspect of
展示了
JFR and this is the concept of self
JFR，这是自我的概念
describing data here James see did not
James在这里描述数据没有
need any particular changes in order to
需要任何特殊的更改以
display my custom event instead the
显示我的自定义事件，而不是
custom event contained the metadata for
自定义事件包含的元数据
a consumer to represent this information
消费者代表此信息
as a specific example we can expect the
作为一个具体的例子，我们可以期待
ratio field here and as you can see the
比率字段，如您所见
tool is able to render this value as a
工具能够将此值呈现为
centage this is made possible because
之所以可以做到这一点，是因为
the custom event has been decorated with
自定义事件已装饰有
semantic metadata that effectively says
有效说明语义元数据
to a consumer this value is a percentage
对消费者来说，这是一个百分比
so let's summarize the operations you
让我们总结一下您的操作
saw me demonstrate using J command J for
看到我演示了如何使用J命令J
dump a completely mechanical should
抛弃完全机械的东西
ideally be handed by a monitoring tool
理想情况下应由监控工具处理
such a monitoring tool could evoke dump
这样的监视工具可能引起转储
operations as a consequence of something
因某事而进行的操作
happening at the higher level may be a
发生在更高层次上可能是
distributed transaction if we can
如果可以的话，进行分布式交易
expedite the process of getting analysis
加快分析过程
started most likely through some means
最有可能通过某种方式开始
of automation the faster we can
自动化的速度越快
understand and solve problems as of JDK
从JDK开始理解和解决问题
9 Java API and JDK j4 allow programs to
9 Java API和JDK j4允许程序
create and integrate their own events we
创建和整合自己的活动，我们
really hope you like JDK 11 thank you
真的希望你喜欢JDK 11谢谢
for watching
观看